Guide to the Yale College Student Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Yale College student grade lists, 1996-2001; Accession 2005-A-116
  - Child Study, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 471)
  - Chinese, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 472)
  - Classics, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 473)
  - Classic Civilizations, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 474)
  - College Seminars, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 475)
  - Comparative Literature, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 476)
  - Computer Science, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 477)
  - Czech, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 478)
  - DeVane, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 479)
  - Divinity School, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 480)
  - Drama School, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 481)
  - Economics, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 482)
  - East Asian Studies, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 483)
  - Electrical Engineering, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 484)
  - English, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 485)
  - EPandE, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 486)
  - Engineering and Applied Science, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 487)
  - Ex-Path, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 488)
  - Film Studies, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 489)
  - Forestry and Environmental Studies, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 490)
  - French, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 491)
  - Geology and Geophysics, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 492)
  - German, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 493)
  - German Studies, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 494)
  - Greek, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 495)
  - History, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 496)
  - HPA, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 497)
  - History of Art, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 498)
  - HsPltcs (D.S.), 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 499)
  - History of Science, History of Medicine, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 500)
  - Humanities, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 501)
  - Imbiology, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 502)
  - Indonensian, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 503)
  - International Studies, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 504)
  - Italian, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 505)
  - Japanese, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 506)
  - Judaic Studies, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 507)
  - Korean, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 508)
  - Latin, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 509)
  - Latin American Studies, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 510)
  - Law School, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 511)
  - Linguistics, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 512)
  - Literature, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 513)
  - Literature (D.S.), 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 514)
  - Management, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 515)
  - Math, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 516)
  - Mechanical Engineering, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 517)
  - MBandB, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 518)
  - Music, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 519)
  - Music School, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 520)
  - Near East, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 521)
  - Organismal Biology, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 522)
  - Operations Research, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 523)
  - Pharm, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 524)
  - Philosophy, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 525)
  - Philosophy (D.S.), 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 526)
  - Physics, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 527)
  - Polish, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 528)
  - Political Science, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 529)
  - Portuguese, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 530)
  - Psychology, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 531)
  - PPM, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 532)
  - Religious Studies, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 533)
  - Russian and E.E., 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 534)
  - Russian, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 535)
  - Science, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 536)
  - Slavic, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 537)
  - Sociology, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 538)
  - Spanish, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 539)
  - Special Divisional, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 540)
  - Statistics, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 541)
  - Studies of the Environment, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 542)
  - Teacher Prep, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 543)
  - Theater Studies, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 544)
  - Ukraine, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 545)
  - Women's Studies, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 546)
  - African and Afro-American Studies, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 547)
  - American Studies, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 548)
  - Anthropology, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 549)
  - Applied Math, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 550)
  - Applied Physics, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 551)
  - Archaeology, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 552)
  - Art, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 553)
  - Astronomy, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 554)
  - Biology, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 555)
  - Biomedical Engineering, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 556)
  - British Studies, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 557)
  - Chemical Engineering, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 558)
  - Chemistry, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 559)
  - Child Study, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 560)
  - Chinese, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 561)
  - Classics, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 562)
  - Classic Civilizations, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 563)
  - College Seminars, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 564)
  - Comparative Literature, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 565)
  - Computer Science, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 566)
  - Czech, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 567)
  - DeVane, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 568)
  - Divinity School, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 569)
  - Drama School, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 570)
  - East Asian Studies, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 571)
  - Economics, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 572)
  - Electrical Engineering, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 573)
  - EMD, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 574)
  - English, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 575)
  - EPandE, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 576)
  - Ethnicity, Race andMigration, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 577)
  - Engineering and Applied Science, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 578)
  - Ex Path, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 579)
  - Film Studies, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 580)
  - Forestry and Environmental Studies, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 581)
  - French, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 582)
  - Geology and Geophysics, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 583)
  - German, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 584)
  - German Spec, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 585)
  - German Studies, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 586)
  - Greek, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 587)
  - History, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 588)
  - History of Art, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 589)
  - HsPltcs (D.S.), 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 590)
  - History of Science, History of Medicine, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 591)
  - Humanities, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 592)
  - Indonensian, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 593)
  - International Studies, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 594)
  - Italian, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 595)
  - Japanese, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 596)
  - Korean, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 597)
  - Latin, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 598)
  - Latin American Studies, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 599)
  - Law School, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 600)
  - Linguistics, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 601)
  - Literature, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 602)
  - Literature (D.S.), 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 603)
  - Math, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 604)
  - Mechanical Engineering, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 605)
  - MBandB, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 606)
  - Music, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 607)
  - Music School, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 608)
  - Near East, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 609)
  - Neurbiology, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 610)
  - Organismal Biology, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 611)
  - Pharm, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 612)
  - Philosophy, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 613)
  - Philosophy (D.S.), 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 614)
  - Physics, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 615)
  - Polish, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 616)
  - Political Science, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 617)
  - Portuguese, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 618)
  - Psychology, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 619)
  - PPM, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 620)
  - Religious Studies, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 621)
  - Renaissance, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 622)
  - Russian and E.E., 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 623)
  - Russian, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 624)
  - Science, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 625)
  - Slavic Lang and Lit, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 626)
  - Sociology, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 627)
  - Spanish, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 628)
  - Special Divisional, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 629)
  - Statistics, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 630)
  - Study of the City, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 631)
  - Studies of the Environment, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 632)
  - Teacher Prep, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 633)
  - Theater Studies, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 634)
  - Ukraine, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 635)
  - Women's Studies, 1998 Spring (Box 7, Folder 636)
  - Majors, Spring 1998-1999 (Box 7A, Folder 637)
  - African Studies, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 638)
  - African and Afro-American Studies, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 639)
  - American Studies, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 640)
  - Anthropology, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 641)
  - Applied Math, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 642)
  - Applied Physics, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 643)
  - Archaeology, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 644)
  - Architecture, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 645)
  - Art, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 646)
  - Astronomy, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 647)
  - Biomedical Engineering, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 648)
  - British Studies, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 649)
  - Cell Biology, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 650)
  - Chemical Engineering, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 651)
  - Chemistry, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 652)
  - Child Study, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 653)
  - Chinese, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 654)
  - Classics, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 655)
  - Classic Civilizations, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 656)
  - College Seminars, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 657)
  - Comparative Literature, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 658)
  - Computer Science, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 659)
  - Czech, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 660)
  - Divinity School, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 661)
  - Drama School, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 662)
  - East Asian Studies, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 663)
  - Economics, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 664)
  - Ecology and Evolutionary Biology, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 665)
  - Electrical Engineering, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 666)
  - English, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 667)
  - EPandE, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 668)
  - Engineering and Applied Science, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 669)
  - Ex Path, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 670)
  - Film Studies, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 671)
  - Forestry and Environmental Studies, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 672)
  - French, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 673)
  - Geology and Geophysics, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 674)
  - German, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 675)
  - German Studies, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 676)
  - Greek, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 677)
  - History, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 678)
  - History of Art, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 679)
  - HsPltcs (D.S.), 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 680)
  - History of Science, History of Medicine, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 681)
  - Humanities, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 682)
  - IHD, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 683)
  - Indonensian, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 684)
  - International Studies, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 685)
  - Italian, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 686)
  - Japanese, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 687)
  - Judaic Studies, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 688)
  - Korean, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 689)
  - Latin, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 690)
  - Latin American Studies, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 691)
  - Law School, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 692)
  - Linguistics, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 693)
  - Literature, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 694)
  - Literature (D.S.), 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 695)
  - Luce, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 696)
  - Math, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 697)
  - Management, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 698)
  - MCDB, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 699)
  - Mechanical Engineering, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 700)
  - MBandB, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 701)
  - Music, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 702)
  - Music School, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 703)
  - Near East, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 704)
  - Operations Research, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 705)
  - Organismal Biology, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 706)
  - Philosophy, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 707)
  - Philosophy (D.S.), 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 708)
  - Physics, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 709)
  - Polish, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 710)
  - Political Science, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 711)
  - Portuguese, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 712)
  - Psychology, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 713)
  - Pharmacology, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 714)
  - Religious Studies, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 715)
  - Russian and E.E., 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 716)
  - Russian, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 717)
  - Science, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 718)
  - Slavic Lang and Lit, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 719)
  - Sociology, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 720)
  - Spanish, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 721)
  - Special Divisional, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 722)
  - Statistics, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 723)
  - Study of the City, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 724)
  - Studies of the Environment, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 725)
  - Teacher Prep, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 726)
  - Theater Studies, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 727)
  - Ukrainian, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 728)
  - Women's and Gender Studies, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 729)
  - African Studies, 2000 Spring (Box 9, Folder 730)
  - African and Afro-American Studies, 2000 Spring (Box 9, Folder 731)
  - American Studies, 2000 Spring (Box 9, Folder 732)
  - Anthropology, 2000 Spring (Box 9, Folder 733)
  - Applied Math, 2000 Spring (Box 9, Folder 734)
  - Applied Physics, 2000 Spring (Box 9, Folder 735)
  - Archaeological Studies, 2000 Spring (Box 9, Folder 736)
  - Architecture, 2000 Spring (Box 9, Folder 737)
  - Art, 2000 Spring (Box 9, Folder 738)
  - Astronomy, 2000 Spring (Box 9, Folder 739)
  - Biomedical Engineering, 2000 Spring (Box 9, Folder 740)
  - British Studies, 2000 Spring (Box 9, Folder 741)
  - Chemical Engineering, 2000 Spring (Box 9, Folder 742)
  - Chemistry, 2000 Spring (Box 9, Folder 743)
  - Child Study, 2000 Spring (Box 9, Folder 744)
  - Chinese, 2000 Spring (Box 9, Folder 745)
  - Classics, 2000 Spring (Box 9, Folder 746)
  - Classic Civilizations, 2000 Spring (Box 9, Folder 747)
  - College Seminars, 2000 Spring (Box 9, Folder 748)
  - Comparative Literature, 2000 Spring (Box 9, Folder 749)
  - Computer Science, 2000 Spring (Box 9, Folder 750)
  - Czech, 2000 Spring (Box 9, Folder 751)
  - Drama School, 2000 Spring (Box 9, Folder 752)
  - East Asian Studies, 2000 Spring (Box 9, Folder 753)
  - Ecology and Evolutionary Biology, 2000 Spring (Box 9, Folder 754)
  - Economics, 2000 Spring (Box 9, Folder 755)
  - Electrical Engineering, 2000 Spring (Box 9, Folder 756)
  - Engineering and Applied Science, 2000 Spring (Box 9, Folder 757)
  - English, 2000 Spring (Box 9, Folder 758)
  - Ethics Politics and Economics, 2000 Spring (Box 9, Folder 759)
  - Ethnicity Race and Migration, 2000 Spring (Box 9, Folder 760)
  - Film Studies, 2000 Spring (Box 9, Folder 761)
  - Forestry and Environmental Studies, 2000 Spring (Box 9, Folder 762)
  - French, 2000 Spring (Box 9, Folder 763)
  - Geology and Geophysics, 2000 Spring (Box 9, Folder 764)
  - German, 2000 Spring (Box 9, Folder 765)
  - German Studies, 2000 Spring (Box 9, Folder 766)
  - Greek, 2000 Spring (Box 9, Folder 767)
  - Hindi, 2000 Spring (Box 9, Folder 768)
  - History, 2000 Spring (Box 9, Folder 769)
  - History of Art, 2000 Spring (Box 9, Folder 770)
  - HsPltcs (D.S.), 2000 Spring (Box 9, Folder 771)
  - History of Science, History of Medicine, 2000 Spring (Box 9, Folder 772)
  - Humanities, 2000 Spring (Box 9, Folder 773)
  - HPA, 2000 Spring (Box 9, Folder 774)
  - Indonensian, 2000 Spring (Box 9, Folder 775)
  - International Studies, 2000 Spring (Box 9, Folder 776)
  - Italian, 2000 Spring (Box 10, Folder 777)
  - Japanese, 2000 Spring (Box 10, Folder 778)
  - Judaic Studies, 2000 Spring (Box 10, Folder 779)
  - Korean, 2000 Spring (Box 10, Folder 780)
  - Latin, 2000 Spring (Box 10, Folder 781)
  - Law School, 2000 Spring (Box 10, Folder 782)
  - Linguistics, 2000 Spring (Box 10, Folder 783)
  - Literature, 2000 Spring (Box 10, Folder 784)
  - Literature (D.S.), 2000 Spring (Box 10, Folder 785)
  - Management, 2000 Spring (Box 10, Folder 786)
  - Math, 2000 Spring (Box 10, Folder 787)
  - MCDB, 2000 Spring (Box 10, Folder 788)
  - Mechanical Engineering, 2000 Spring (Box 10, Folder 789)
  - MBandB, 2000 Spring (Box 10, Folder 790)
  - Music, 2000 Spring (Box 10, Folder 791)
  - Music School, 2000 Spring (Box 10, Folder 792)
  - Near East, 2000 Spring (Box 10, Folder 793)
  - Neuroscience, 2000 Spring (Box 10, Folder 794)
  - Operations Research, 2000 Spring (Box 10, Folder 795)
  - Pathology, 2000 Spring (Box 10, Folder 796)
  - Philosophy, 2000 Spring (Box 10, Folder 797)
  - Philosophy (D.S.), 2000 Spring (Box 10, Folder 798)
  - Physics, 2000 Spring (Box 10, Folder 799)
  - Polish, 2000 Spring (Box 10, Folder 800)
  - Political Science, 2000 Spring (Box 10, Folder 801)
  - Portuguese, 2000 Spring (Box 10, Folder 802)
  - Psychology, 2000 Spring (Box 10, Folder 803)
  - Religious Studies, 2000 Spring (Box 10, Folder 804)
  - Russian and E.E., 2000 Spring (Box 10, Folder 805)
  - Russian, 2000 Spring (Box 10, Folder 806)
  - Serbo-Croatian, 2000 Spring (Box 10, Folder 807)
  - Science, 2000 Spring (Box 10, Folder 808)
  - Slavic Lang and Lit, 2000 Spring (Box 10, Folder 809)
  - Sociology, 2000 Spring (Box 10, Folder 810)
  - Spanish, 2000 Spring (Box 10, Folder 811)
  - Special Divisional, 2000 Spring (Box 10, Folder 812)
  - Statistics, 2000 Spring (Box 10, Folder 813)
  - Study of the City, 2000 Spring (Box 10, Folder 814)
  - Studies of the Environment, 2000 Spring (Box 10, Folder 815)
  - Teacher Prep, 2000 Spring (Box 10, Folder 816)
  - Theater Studies, 2000 Spring (Box 10, Folder 817)
  - Ukranian, 2000 Spring (Box 10, Folder 818)
  - Vietnamese, 2000 Spring (Box 10, Folder 819)
  - Women's and Gender Studies, 2000 Spring (Box 10, Folder 820)
  - African Studies, 2001 Spring (Box 11, Folder 821)
  - African-American Studies, 2001 Spring (Box 11, Folder 822)
  - American Studies, 2001 Spring (Box 11, Folder 823)
  - Anthropology, 2001 Spring (Box 11, Folder 824)
  - Applied Math, 2001 Spring (Box 11, Folder 825)
  - Applied Physics, 2001 Spring (Box 11, Folder 826)
  - Archaeological Studies, 2001 Spring (Box 11, Folder 827)
  - Architecture, 2001 Spring (Box 11, Folder 828)
  - Art, 2001 Spring (Box 11, Folder 829)
  - Astronomy, 2001 Spring (Box 11, Folder 830)
  - Biomedical Engineering, 2001 Spring (Box 11, Folder 831)
  - British Studies, 2001 Spring (Box 11, Folder 832)
  - Chemical Engineering, 2001 Spring (Box 11, Folder 833)
  - Chemistry, 2001 Spring (Box 11, Folder 834)
  - Child Study, 2001 Spring (Box 11, Folder 835)
  - Chinese, 2001 Spring (Box 11, Folder 836)
  - Classics, 2001 Spring (Box 11, Folder 837)
  - Classic Civilizations, 2001 Spring (Box 11, Folder 838)
  - Cognitive Science, 2001 Spring (Box 11, Folder 839)
  - College Seminars, 2001 Spring (Box 11, Folder 840)
  - Computer Science, 2001 Spring (Box 11, Folder 841)
  - DeVane, 2001 Spring (Box 11, Folder 842)
  - Drama School, 2001 Spring (Box 11, Folder 843)
  - East Asian Studies, 2001 Spring (Box 11, Folder 844)
  - Ecology and Evolutionary Biology, 2001 Spring (Box 11, Folder 845)
  - Economics, 2001 Spring (Box 11, Folder 846)
  - Electrical Engineering, 2001 Spring (Box 11, Folder 847)
  - Engineering and Applied Science, 2001 Spring (Box 11, Folder 848)
  - English, 2001 Spring (Box 11, Folder 849)
  - Environmental Engineering, 2001 Spring (Box 11, Folder 850)
  - EMD, 2001 Spring (Box 11, Folder 851)
  - Ethics Politics and Economics, 2001 Spring (Box 11, Folder 852)
  - Ethnicity Race and Migration, 2001 Spring (Box 11, Folder 853)
  - Film Studies, 2001 Spring (Box 11, Folder 854)
  - Forestry and Environmental Studies, 2001 Spring (Box 11, Folder 855)
  - French, 2001 Spring (Box 11, Folder 856)
  - Geology and Geophysics, 2001 Spring (Box 11, Folder 857)
  - German, 2001 Spring (Box 11, Folder 858)
  - German Studies, 2001 Spring (Box 11, Folder 859)
  - GHD (Epidemiology and Public Health), 2001 Spring (Box 12, Folder 860)
  - Greek, 2001 Spring (Box 12, Folder 861)
  - HPA (Health Public Administration), 2001 Spring (Box 12, Folder 862)
  - Hindi, 2001 Spring (Box 12, Folder 863)
  - History, 2001 Spring (Box 12, Folder 864)
  - History of Art, 2001 Spring (Box 12, Folder 865)
  - HsPltcs (D.S.), 2001 Spring (Box 12, Folder 866)
  - History of Science, History of Medicine, 2001 Spring (Box 12, Folder 867)
  - Humanities, 2001 Spring (Box 12, Folder 868)
  - Indic, 2001 Spring (Box 12, Folder 869)
  - International Studies, 2001 Spring (Box 12, Folder 870)
  - Italian, 2001 Spring (Box 12, Folder 871)
  - Judaic Studies, 2001 Spring (Box 12, Folder 872)
  - Japanese, 2001 Spring (Box 12, Folder 873)
  - Judaic Studies, 2001 Spring (Box 12, Folder 874)
  - Korean, 2001 Spring (Box 12, Folder 875)
  - Latin, 2001 Spring (Box 12, Folder 876)
  - Latin American Studies, 2001 Spring (Box 12, Folder 877)
  - Law School, 2001 Spring (Box 12, Folder 878)
  - Linguistics, 2001 Spring (Box 12, Folder 879)
  - Literature, 2001 Spring (Box 12, Folder 880)
  - Literature (D.S.), 2001 Spring (Box 12, Folder 881)
  - Management, 2001 Spring (Box 12, Folder 882)
  - Math, 2001 Spring (Box 12, Folder 883)
  - MCDB, 2001 Spring (Box 12, Folder 884)
  - Mechanical Engineering, 2001 Spring (Box 12, Folder 885)
  - MBandB, 2001 Spring (Box 12, Folder 886)
  - MBio (EPH), 2001 Spring (Box 12, Folder 887)
  - Music, 2001 Spring (Box 12, Folder 888)
  - Music School, 2001 Spring (Box 12, Folder 889)
  - Near East Languages, 2001 Spring (Box 12, Folder 890)
  - Operations Research, 2001 Spring (Box 12, Folder 891)
  - Pathology, 2001 Spring (Box 12, Folder 892)
  - Philosophy, 2001 Spring (Box 12, Folder 893)
  - Philosophy (D.S.), 2001 Spring (Box 12, Folder 894)
  - Physics, 2001 Spring (Box 12, Folder 895)
  - Polish, 2001 Spring (Box 12, Folder 896)
  - Political Science, 2001 Spring (Box 12, Folder 897)
  - Portuguese, 2001 Spring (Box 12, Folder 898)
  - Psychology, 2001 Spring (Box 12, Folder 899)
  - Religious Studies, 2001 Spring (Box 12, Folder 900)
  - Renaissance Studies, 2001 Spring (Box 12, Folder 901)
  - Russian and E.E., 2001 Spring (Box 12, Folder 902)
  - Russian, 2001 Spring (Box 12, Folder 903)
  - Slavic Lang and Lit, 2001 Spring (Box 12, Folder 904)
  - Sociology, 2001 Spring (Box 12, Folder 905)
  - Spanish, 2001 Spring (Box 12, Folder 906)
  - Special Divisional, 2001 Spring (Box 12, Folder 907)
  - Statistics, 2001 Spring (Box 12, Folder 908)
  - Studies of the Environment, 2001 Spring (Box 12, Folder 909)
  - Study of the City, 2001 Spring (Box 12, Folder 910)
  - Teacher Prep, 2001 Spring (Box 12, Folder 911)
  - Theater Studies, 2001 Spring (Box 12, Folder 912)
  - Ukranian, 2001 Spring (Box 12, Folder 913)
  - Vietnamese, 2001 Spring (Box 12, Folder 914)
  - Women's and Gender Studies, 2001 Spring (Box 12, Folder 915)
- Yale College Grade Sheets, Fall 2001; Accession 2005-A-146
  Arranged alphabetically by department.
  - Senior Distribution, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Accounting, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - African Studies, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - African-American Studies, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - American Studies, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Anthropology, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Applied Math, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Applied Physics, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Archaeological Studies, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Architecture, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Art, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Astronomy, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Biomedical Engineering, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - BIS, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - British Studies, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 15)